hair's looking at you kid hair's looking
at you
kid there's one thing the internet has
taught me it's said my current haircut
is the worst thing to happen on
television since the Lost finale
uh
well it's just the rest of my hair is in
purgatory that's what it is uh people
keep asking me what were you thinking
and I was like I don't know it's hair it
grows back who gives a but
comedians I'm going to show you some
truly horrifying haircuts from the
subreddit just my up and I want I
want you to tell me what they told the
barber to do I'm going to start the
clock now first
one great Ferguson make me look like I'm
just being born yes
pun next one Seth make me look like
burning man Andy Samberg
yes great poops you think SeaWorld's
cruel to whales
points greig Ferguson I want to look
like I'm too short for my mustache
[Music]
[Applause]
points